var examdatabase =
{
     "questiontemplate": {
        "question": "What is the answer?",
        "lquestion": "latex reformatting for questions that needed it, absent if not needed",
        "answer": "That which was asked for",
        "lanswer": "latex reformatting for answers that needed it, absent if not needed",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C num -- number of class where this material was covered"
     },
  "description": "questions from which to construct the Fall 2017 quizzes in CS4472a",
  "questions": [
     {
        "question": "To illustrate the relation between testing and software design, we will look at the programming technique ANSWER",
        "answer": "test driven development",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C1"
     },
     {
        "question": "An important concept we will look at related to the question of when has one done enough testing is ANSWER",
        "answer": ["coverage","mutation"],
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C1"
     },
     {
        "question": "It is easy to make up test inputs, but it can be tricky to know what the right output for a given input should be.  This is refered to as the ANSWER problem",
        "answer": "Oracle",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C1"
     },
     {
        "question": "Testing is generally about finding errors that have already been made.  This course also covers the topic of ANSWER, which is about trying to prevent errors from being made in the first place.",
        "answer": "quality assurance",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C1"
     },
     {
        "question": "The first testing framework for Ruby that we are looking at is called ANSWER",
        "answer": "minitest",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C1"
     },
     {
        "question": "The first tool for checking code quality for programs written in Ruby is ANSWER, which is described as a code smell detector.",
        "answer": "reek",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C1"
     },
     {
        "question": "The number of quizzes CS4472 will have this semester is ANSWER",
        "answer": "3",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C1"
     },
     {
        "question": "The number of weekly practices that CS4472 will have this semester is ANSWER",
        "answer": "10",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C1"
     },
     {
        "question": "The number of practice reviews that CS4472 will have this semester is ANSWER",
        "answer": "4",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C1"
     },
     {
        "question": "The per cent of the total mark allocated for all the quizzes is ANSWER",
        "answer": "21",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C1"
     },
     {
        "question": "The per cent of the total mark allocated for all the weekly practices is ANSWER",
        "answer": "30",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C1"
     },
     {
        "question": "The per cent of the total mark allocated for all the practice reviews is ANSWER",
        "answer": "49",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C1"
     },
     {
        "question": "The practice technique advocated in this class is a modification of the ANSWER",
        "answer": "Personal Software Process",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C2"
     },
     {
        "question": "A main theme behind the practice technique advocated in this class is that in order to improve your programming, ANSWER",
        "answer": "you need data about your past programming",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C2"
     },
     {
        "question": "A common piece of information for people interested in programmer productivity to track is ANSWER",
        "answer": ["time spent","number of lines of code written","number of defects found"],
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C2"
     },
     {
        "question": "Although we often think of programs as taking inputs and producing outputs, a higher level view of what is going on is to think of the programs as ANSWER about how to take inputs and produce outputs.",
        "answer": "encode knowledge",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C2"
     },
     {
        "question": "The scripts that were designed to aid the practice process assume that you will be uploading a copy of your work to BitBucket every time you ANSWER",
        "answer": "record a note about your practice progress",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C2"
     },
     {
        "question": "The protocols for practice expect that the longest amount of time that you will practice before recording a note is ANSWER",
        "answer": "30 minutes",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C2"
     },
     {
        "question": "The total amount of practice time you can get credit for during a practice week is ANSWER",
        "answer": "3 hours",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C2"
     },
     {
        "question": "The four phases of testing (according to Whittaker) are: 1) modeling the software environment, 2) selecting test cases, 3) running and checking test cases, and 4) ANSWER",
        "answer": "checking how well the testing is going",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C3"
     },
     {
        "question": "The testing technique called boundary value partition starts with the notion of breaking the space of inputs into ANSWER",
        "answer": "regions of interest",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C3"
     },
     {
        "question": "Structural testing is another name for ANSWER",
        "answer": ["code-based testing","white-box testing"],
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C3"
     },
     {
        "question": "The kind of testing we do to make sure that when we change a program we do not break something that used to work is called ANSWER",
        "answer": "regression testing",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C3"
     },
     {
        "question": "Using combinatorial testing, if I have 10 binary inputs, I only need to use ANSWER test cases (each a setting of each of the 10 inputs) to expect to find 98 per cent of the errors in the program.",
        "answer": "13",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C3"
     },
     {
        "question": "The ANSWER is a method developed by Watt S. Humphrey to help individuals improve their programming skills based on existing methods that had been developed to help organizations improve their product development capabilities.",
        "answer": "Personal Software Process",
        "note": "optional note",
        "source": "C3"
     },
    null
  ]
}
